1 EEGNet: a compact convolutional neural network for EEG-based brainûcomputer inte | not specified
2 A review of classification algorithms for EEG-based brainûcomputer interfaces: a | not specified
3 Towards passive brainûcomputer interfaces: applying brainûcomputer interface tec | not specified
4 EEG-Based Brain-Computer Interfaces Using Motor-Imagery: Techniques and Challeng | not specified
5 Enhanced performance by a hybrid NIRSûEEG brain computer interface | not specified
6 Combining brain-computer interfaces and assistive technologies: state-of-the-art | not specified
7 Current Status, Challenges, and Possible Solutions of EEG-Based Brain-Computer I | not specified
8 Deep learning-based electroencephalography analysis: a systematic review | not specified
9 Brain computer interfacing: Applications and challenges | not specified
10 Adaptive Automation Triggered by EEG-Based Mental Workload Index: A Passive Brai | 12 participants
11 Deep learning with convolutional neural networks for EEG decoding and visualizat | not specified
12 Deep learning for electroencephalogram (EEG) classification tasks: a review | not specified
13 Understanding Cognitive Load in Digital and Online Learning: a New Perspective o | not specified
14 Enhancing learning experiences: EEG-based passive BCI system adapts learning spe | not specified
15 Cognitive load theory, educational research, and instructional design: some food | not specified
16 Challenging Cognitive Load Theory: The Role of Educational Neuroscience and Arti | not specified
17 Cognitive Architecture and Instructional Design: 20 Years Later | not specified
18 The Cognitive Neuroscience of Working Memory | not specified
19 
